LHCP-X by
_________  __                   __             
\    ___ \|  |__  __ __  ____  |__| ____  ____ 
/    \  \/|  |  \|  |  \/    \ |  |/ __ \/ __ \
\     \___|      \  |  /   |  \|  |  ___|  ___|
 \________/___|  /____/|_/\|__/|  |\____/_____/
               \/        \________|     Chunjee
This software is copyright 2015 - DownloadMob.com - all rights reserved.

LEGAL:
THIS SOFTWARE COMES WITH NO WARRANTIES, USE AT YOUR OWN RISK, YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE INCURED
Don't claim my work as your own.
Please give me credit for my work. Chunjee - DownloadMob.com
You may sell this to any sucker(s) you can find, but please send me a cut yo.

MORE LEGAL:
By downloading and/or using the software, you are knowingly and voluntarily assuming all risk of loss or damage in connection with the software.
You are required to take all reasonable measures to avoid and reduce damages, including but not limited to making back-up copies of all your computer data. In no event will downloadmob, including but not limited to Chunjee, be liable to you for any direct damages, claims or costs whatsoever and/or any indirect, consequential, incidental damages, or any lost profits or lost savings; any loss of use, revenue or profit; any lost or damaged data; downtime; and/or any other commercial or economic loss even if a hitachi representative has been advised of the possibility of such loss, damages, claims or costs or for any claim by any third party.